http://www.transfcu.com/?page=privacy_policy

Search Our Site!
Accounts
Checking AccountsSavings AccountsShare CertificatesIRA AccountsPackaged Accounts
Loans
NEW: Holiday Loans Vehicle LoansCar Buying ServicePersonal & Other LoansMake a Loan Payment Credit CardsHome Equity LoansMortgage LoansStudent Choice LoansBoat and RV
Convenience
Account AccessMobile AccessMobile DepositApple PayCO-OP ATMs & Shared BranchesPayments & TransfersTelephone AssistanceVISA Debit CardsCalculators
Rates
RatesFees
Service
Information & EducationProtecting YourselfInsurance OptionsGreenPath Financial WellnessScholarship Opportunities
Forms
SavingsLoansAdd_ChangeAffidavitsDisputesServices
About
About UsOur 5-Star RatingThe Benefits of MembershipJoin UsTFCU Branch & ATM LocationsJob OpportunitiesBoard of DirectorsSecurityPrivacy
Contact
Find ATM
Privacy Policy
Revised 4/2014
FACTS
WHAT DOES TRANSPORTATION FCU DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share,
and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and account transactions;
account balances and payment history;
and credit history.
How?
All financial companies need to share members' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members' personal information; the reasons Transportation FCU chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
DoesTransportation FCU share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes— such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes— to offer our products and services to you
Yes
Yes
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
Yes
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes— information about your transactions and experiences
Yes
No
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes— information about your creditworthiness
No
We don't share
For our affiliates to market to you
Yes
Yes
For non-affiliates to market to you
No
We don't share
To limit our sharing
Call 202-366-9400 or 800-368-8432
Please note:
If you are a new member, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our member, we do not share information, except as required or permitted by law.
Questions?
Call 800-368-8432
What we do
How does Transportation FCU protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with all applicable laws and regulations. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
We maintain physical, electronic, or procedural safeguards that complywith federal laws and regulations to guard your non-public personal information.
How does Transportation FCU collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
open an account or apply for a loan
pay your bills or make deposit or withdrawals from your account
give us your contact information
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?
Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies. Our affiliates include financial companies such as Credit Union Service Organizations, insurance companies and others.
Non-affiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
TFCU does not share with non-affiliates
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include PSCU and CUNA Mutual.
NEW: Holiday Loans Vehicle LoansCar Buying ServicePersonal & Other LoansMake a Loan Payment Credit CardsHome Equity LoansMortgage LoansStudent Choice LoansBoat and RV
Application Center
Join or Add Account
Apply for a Loan
Check Application Status
Current Rates
ATM Locator
We'll make sure you're informed and ready for your next step.
Your financial journey should be smooth and worry-free.
There are lots of ways to stay connected to your money.
We're with you every step of the way.
